hello everyone this is kangsha
gangapuram and you're watching hibis
news
adding the wide range of insurance
solutions avail to the customers on its
platform atl payments bank has started
offering cyber insurance in partnership
with icici lombard general insurance
company growth in digital payments and
transactions has also led a surge in
online frauds that are becoming
increasingly sophisticated the cyber
insurance solutions from icici lombard
provides financial protection to
customers against potential financial
frauds relating to bank credit cards or
debit cards identity thefts phishing or
email spoofing and more mr sanjeev
mantri executive director icici lombard
said we are excited to partner with atl
payments bank as the pioneer triumph
will assert the company's pledge to
provide innovative new age risk
solutions to our customers to prevent
cyber attacks exploiting in the era of
digital transformation mr ganesh anantha
narayanan chief operating officer ital
payments bank said we are pleased to
partner with icici lombard to offer this
product to the customers it is an
important addition to our existing body
queue of simple secure and value driven
solutions and we hope our users will
seek the advantage of this unique
offering thank you for watching hibis
news
you